我想问一个问题  你们当中有哪一个人
Janice has a question. Who of the six of you...
跟你们当中的另一个人睡过
has slept with who of the six of you?
好色的数学问题
Wow, it's like a dirty math problem.
很抱歉  答案是一个也没有
I'm sorry, the answer there would be none of us.
这么多年
Come on, over the years,
你们难道没有喝醉做过蠢事吗
none of you ever got, you know drunk and stupid?
那是另外一个问题
Well, that's really a different question.
抱歉  我很难相信
I'm sorry I find it hard to believe
一群成天混在一起的人
that a group of people who spends this much time together...
居然没爆过丑闻
as you guys do has never bumped uglies.
有一次  莫妮卡曾经和瑞秋在一起
There was that one time Monica and Rachel got together.
什么
What?
你说什么呢  没有"有一次"
Excuse me, there was no "time."
那就假设有
Okay, but let's say there was.
会怎么样
How might that go?
好吧好吧  那就告诉我
Okay, okay, well then answer me this:
你们有没有差一点...
Have any of you ever almost...?
-还有谁要咖啡  -外面有狗狗
- Anybody need more coffee? - Hey,there's a dog out there!
-太可惜了  -怎么了
- That is so unfortunate. - What?
可爱裸男越来越肥了
Cute naked guy is really starting to put on weight.
我马上回来
Okay, I'll be back in just a minute.
菲比  抱歉我的口红印到电话筒上了
Phoebe, I'm sorry that I left lipstick marks on the phone.
你没有在电话上留下口红印啊
You didn't leave lipstick marks on the phone.
那肯定是你干的  再见
Then it must have been you. Bye.
走好不送
Bye-bye.
-所以我才要搬走  -说到这件事
- That's why I moved out. - Hey, while we're on that...
你准备什么时候告诉我老妹  你不住这里了
when are you gonna tell my sister you don't live here anymore?
在某种程度上  她已经知道了
I think on some level, she already knows.
菲比  她不知道你每天晚上溜出去
Phoebe, she doesn't know you sneak out every night...
她不知道你每天早上溜回来
she doesn't know that you sneak back every morning...
她也不知道你已经去外婆家
and she doesn't know that you've been living with
住一个星期了
your Grandmother's for a week now.
好吧  也许还没到这个程度
Okay, well, maybe not on those levels.
我永远也找不到室友了
I'm never gonna find a roommate. Ever.
没有好人选
Nobody good?
想想看  有个家伙养了雪貂
Let's see. There was the guy with the ferrets.
是一堆哦
That's plural.
有一个爱吐口水
The spitter.
对了  还有一个觉得我的名字很好玩
Oh and yes. The guy who enjoyed my name so much...
每次念都要发出怪声
he felt the need to make a noise every time he said it.
"幸会  钱德勒·宾  叮"
"Nice to meet you,Chandler Bing. Bing!"
"这房子好棒啊  钱德勒·宾  叮"
"Great apartment, Chandler Bing. Bing!"
明天还有几个
So how many more do you have tomorrow?
两个  一个看起来很无趣的摄影师
Two. This photographer who seemed really dull...
和一个捉摸不透的演员
and this actor guy who I'm not sure about.
他打来电话  我说"钱德勒·宾"
Because when he called I answered the phone "Chandler Bing"...
他居然说  "哇  好短的留言啊"
he said, "Whoa! Short message!"
罗斯  把脚放下  否则以后不准来了
Ross, foot on the floor or come over no more.
你的梳妆台都不见了  可她只注意到这个
Your dresser is missing, but this she notices.
-你说什么  -我该走了
- What? - I have to go.
卡罗尔应该回家了  所以...
Carol should be home by now,so....
-你们两个还好吗  -有起色了
- How's it going with you guys? - Better, actually.
我想我终于搞清楚了
You know I think I finally figured out
我们最近总闹别扭的原因
why we're having so much trouble lately.
-真的吗  -对  我有你们这么多好朋友
- Oh, really? - Yeah. You know how I have you guys?
她自己没有要好的朋友
She doesn't have any close friends that are just hers.
不过上星期她在健身房认识了一个
But last week, she met this woman at the gym,
叫苏珊的女人
"Susan" something.
她们一拍即合  我想情况会有不同的
And they really hit it off, and I think it's gonna make a difference.
艾瑞克
So, Eric...
你是哪一种摄影师
what kind of photography do you do?
大部分是流行时尚
Oh,mostly fashion.
所以时不时会有模特过来  没关系吧
So there may be models here from time to time. I hope that's cool.
没关系
Yes, that is cool.
因为我这有模特来的几率
Because I have models here, you know...
是零
never.
还有什么呢  对了
What else? Oh, yeah.
夏天我基本都去我姐的海边小屋度周末
During the summer I spend most weekends at my sister's beach house...
也欢迎你去玩
which you're welcome to use by the way.
不过我得告诉你  她是色情片女星
Although I should probably tell you, she's a porn star.
听我说  我还要见一个人
Well, listen. I still have one more person to meet.
不过除非是你姐姐
But unless it turns out to be your sister...
你的机会应该很大
I think your chances are pretty good.
来吧
All right.
卧房  浴室  客厅
Bedroom, bathroom, living room.
这里是厨房  谢谢你来  再见
This right here is the kitchen, and thanks for coming by. Bye-bye.
你不想问我问题吗
Don't you, don't you wanna ask me any questions?
好
Sure.
你好吗
What's up?
我是演员
Well, I'm an actor.
我很爱干净
I'm fairly neat.
我自己有电视
I got my own TV.
你放心  我不排斥同性恋
Oh, and don't worry, I'm totally okay with the gay thing.
什么同性恋
What gay thing?
就是一般的
Just, you know, in general.
同性恋的那些事
The whole "people-being-gay" thing.
我完全不在意
Totally cool with that.
杰瑞  谢谢你来
Okay, Jerry. Thanks for stopping by.
好帅
Oh, my God!
莫妮卡
Hey, Mon.
-想听一件很烂的事吗  -你见我听过吗
- Wanna hear something that sucks? - Do I ever!
-克里斯说酒吧要停业了  -不会吧
- Chris says they're closing down the bar. - No way!
听说这里要改成一家咖啡馆
Apparently, they're turning it into some kind of coffee place.
只卖咖啡
Just coffee?
-那我们以后去哪里玩  -我怎么知道
- Where are we gonna hang out now? - You got me.
请来瓶啤酒
Can I get a beer please?
室友挑好了吗
Did you pick a roommate?
-那当然  -是那个意大利帅哥吗
- You betcha. - ls it the ltalian guy?
怎么可能
Yeah, right.
他多帅啊
He's so cute.
那正是我想要的  找个帅哥当室友
Yes, that's what I want. A roommate I can walk around with...
我就变成"搞笑那个"
and be referred to as "the funny one."
台球桌空了  准备一下
Pool table's free. Rack them up.
我马上回来
I'll be back in just a minute.
准备让我打屁股吧
Get ready for me to whip your butt.
好  不过之后要打球
Okay, but after that, we're shooting some pool.
不对  很抱歉  麻烦过来下
No no... Excuse me? Hello? Hi.
我朋友点的是洋葱
My friend ordered an onion...
不是橄榄
... not an olive.
我点的是朗姆酒加健怡可乐
And I ordered a rum and Diet Coke...
这杯不是
...which I don't think this is.
-对不起  -没关系
- I am so sorry. - That's all right.
准备饮料能有多难
I mean how hard is it to get a couple drinks right, huh?
好了
Well...
我们来敬酒
I would like to propose a toast...
敬这位女士  一年后的今天就会成为
...to the woman who, in one year from today, will become...
牙科博士  巴瑞·法伯医生夫人
Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber, D.D.S.
我想应该再秀一次戒指了
I think it's time to see the ring again.
很棒吧  就好像一辈子都有男朋友了
Isn't it exciting? I mean, it's like having a boyfriend for life!
是啊  我知道
Yeah. I know.
怎么了
What?
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
也许只是想到
Well, maybe it's just the idea of...
一辈子要跟巴瑞在一起
Barry for the rest of my life.
我不知道  我觉得...
I don't know, I think l....
我想来个最后的放纵
I feel like I need to have one last fling
好永远忘记这种事
you know, just to sort of get it out of my system.
-瑞秋  别说了  -你好坏
- Rachel, stop! - You're so bad!
我说真的  我真的觉得我需要
I'm serious. I really I think I need to just have some
纯欲望的性爱
meaningless sex, you know?
就跟下一个我看到的男人
With the next guy I see.
抱歉  我的球好像掉了
Excuse me, I seem to have dropped my ball.
所以呢
Yeah, so?
我又把它捡起来了
And now I've picked it up again.
天哪  那是我的高中同学
My God! I went to high school with her.
瑞秋  你好
Rachel. Hi.
莫妮卡
Monica!
快看  你觉得如何
Look! Hi! What do you think?
天哪
Oh, my God!
泰坦尼克号撞的地方都看不到
You can't even see where the Titanic hit it.
没错  他叫巴瑞  是一位医生  谢谢
Yes, his name is Barry. He's a doctor, thank you very much.
这是你的梦想  恭喜你
Just like you always wanted. Congratulations.
谢谢  那你呢  有对象吗
Thank you. So how about you? Are you seeing anybody?
目前没有
Not right now.
哎哟  没关系的
Oh, well, that's okay.
我知道
I know.
我要去找我朋友了
So I think I'll get back to my friend.
好的  好的
Oh, yeah. Sure, sure, sure.
下次我来  我们一起吃午饭如何
Listen, can we please have lunch the next time I'm in the city?
好啊
That'd be great.
-好的  再见  -再见
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
十块钱赌我这辈子都不会再见到她
Ten bucks says I never see that woman again in my life.
不  亲爱的  真的没关系
No, honey, really. It's fine.
你就...
Just...
跟苏珊去吧
...go with Susan.
真的  我觉得...
Really, I think
我觉得女生一起出门很好啊
No, I think girls' night out is a great idea.
好的  好的  拜
Okay. Okay. Bye.
她们要做什么
What are they doing?
不知道  女生做的事
I don't know. Something girly.
你回来早了
Hey, you're early.
你拿着那盏灯做什么
What are you doing with the lamp?
拿去换电线
Just taking it to get rewired.
别送去修音响那家
Don't take it to the same place you took the stereo.
他们已经修一星期了
'Cause they've had that for over a week.
没有  哈克先生  我们没有制造噪音
No, no. Mr. Heckles, no one is making any noise up here.
你们打扰我练习双簧管了
You're disturbing my oboe practice.
-你又不会吹双簧管  -我可以吹
- You don't play the oboe. - I could play the oboe.
那就请你小声一点
Then I'm going to have to ask you to keep it down.
你是谁
Who are you?
你好  我是艾瑞克  钱德勒的新室友
Hi, I'm Eric, I'm gonna be Chandler's new roommate.
我才是钱德勒的新室友
I'm Chandler's new roommate.
-不是吧  -我可以当钱德勒的新室友
- I don't think so. - I could be Chandler's new roommate.
但是他打电话告诉我...
But he told me over the phone...
他是亲口告诉我的
He told me in person.
好奇怪
That's weird.
我要回我的新公寓了
I'm going to go into my new apartment now.
又见面了
Hi again.
太谢谢你了
Thank you so much.
别谢我  谢那个没出现的混蛋
No no...Don't thank me. Thank the jerk that didn't showed up.
我要去上班了
Okay, I gotta get to work.
需要帮忙吗
You need some help with that?
不用了  多谢  我可以
No, thanks. I got it.
我不行
No, I don't!
没事吧
Okay?
我起来得太快了  头有点晕
I stood up too fast. Got a little head rush.
太热了
It's the heat.
而且又湿
And the humidity.
加起来
That's...
实在蛮难受的
...a tough combination.
想不想进来喝杯柠檬汁
Do you want to come in for some lemonade?
想得不得了
Like you wouldn't believe.
你家好漂亮
This is a great place.
谢谢
Thank you.
不要客气
Just make yourself comfortable.
懂了
Gotcha.
这其实是我奶奶的房子
So this place is really my grandmother's.
她搬去佛罗里达州  我才能住
I got it from her when she moved to Florida.
否则我根本租不起这样的公寓
Otherwise I could never afford a place like this.
要是房东问起
So if the landlord ever asks...
你就说我是87岁
I'm an 87- year- old woman
害怕录像机的老太太  你渴吗
who's afraid of her VCR. You thirsty?
渴得不得了
You bet I am!
好
Okay...
这是你的老二
... here's your penis!
天哪  你在干什么
Oh, my God! What the hell are you doing?
你问我想不想进来喝柠檬汁
You said, "You wanna come in for some lemonade?"
所以呢
So?
你只是要给我柠檬汁吗
Were you just gonna give me lemonade?
是啊
Ya-huh.
赶快遮起来
Cover yourself up!
对  抱歉
Oh, right. Sorry.
老天  我真不敢相信
God, I don't believe this!
人家请你喝柠檬汁
Someone asks you in for lemonade
你就认为是想跟你上床吗
and to you that means they want to have sex?
通常是啊  不只柠檬汁啦
Usually, yeah. Well, not just lemonade.
冰茶啦  果汁啦
Iced tea, sometimes juice.
我很抱歉  我只是...
Look, sorry. I just
我以为你喜欢我
I thought you liked me.
我真混蛋
I'm such a jerk.
没关系
It's okay.
任何人都会碰上这种事
I suppose it could happen to anyone.
我不认识这种人  不过...
Not anyone I know, but....
我还是看得到
By the way, I can still see it.
菲比
Pheebs?
你的床呢
Where's your bed?
不在屋里吗
It's not in the apartment?
不是吧
No.
居然又发生这种事了
I can't believe this is happening again.
-什么  -好吧  别拷问我了
- What? - Okay, enough with the third degree!
我...  我不住这里了
I-I, I don't live here anymore.
-你在说什么  -对不起
- What are you talking about? - I'm sorry.
我...  我不住这里了
I-I-I, I don't live here anymore.
我不知道该怎么告诉你
I didn't know how to tell you.
但是其他人都知道
But, you know, everybody else knows.
大家都知道
Everybody knows?
这本来是好事  但是我忘了原因
That was supposed to be a good thing. I forget why.
莫妮卡  我...
Monica, I...
知道吗  我曾经一整个月睡不着
Do you know, okay, do you know I couldn't sleep for like a month
就因为一个沙发靠垫  被我沾上了一滴墨水
because I got a dot of ink on one of the sofa cushions?
你可以把它翻面啊
You could've just turned the cushion over.
我也想啊  但另一面沾上了意大利面酱汁
I would have, except I had a big spaghetti stain on the other side.
什么
What?
我就是这个意思
Okay, this is what I'm talking about.
我要住在可以打翻东西的地方
I need to live in a land where people can spill!
你可以打翻东西啊
Well, you can spill.
在水槽里
In the sink.
亲爱的  不是你不好  你就是这样的人
Oh, honey. It's not your fault, you know. This is who you are.
我爱你  我想跟你做朋友
And I love you. And I want us to be friends.
要是我继续住这里  那是不可能的
And if I keep living here, I don't see that happening.
-我也爱你  -那就好
- I love you too. - Good.
怎么了
What?
什么  我只是很难过
What? I'm just sad.
才怪  你在想是哪一个垫子
No, you're not. You're wondering which cushion it is.
在看什么
So what are you watching?
《海滩游侠》
Baywatch.
讲什么的
What's it about?
救生员
Lifeguards.
听起来蛮蠢...
Well, it sounds kind of stup...
她是谁
Who's she?
妮可·艾格
Nicole Eggert.
你会喜欢上她的
You'll like her.
哇  她们在跑
Wow! Look at them run!
她们经常这样
They do that a lot.
你要喝啤酒吗
Hey, you want a beer?
我去拿
Yeah, I'll go get one.
别起来  这有冰桶
No, no. Don't get up. I got a cooler here.
-有人吗  -嘿
- Hello! - Hey.
你有啤酒吗  我们的喝完了
Do you have any beers? We're out of beers.
自己拿
Help yourself.
你还好吗
You okay?
菲比搬走了
Phoebe moved out.
对
Right.
我不懂
I don't understand.
我真的这么难相处吗
Am I so hard to live with?
所以才找不到男朋友吗
Is this why I don't have a boyfriend?
不是  你没有男朋友是因为...
No, you don't have a boyfriend because....
我不知道为什么
I don't know why you don't have a boyfriend.
你应该有男朋友的
You should have a boyfriend.
我也这么认为
I think so.
过来
Come here.
来吧
听我说  你是我最喜欢的人之一
Listen, you are one of my favorite people
还是我在现实中所认识的  最漂亮的女人
and the most beautiful woman I've ever known in real life.
人都在哪里
Where is everybody?
已经关门了  克里斯要我锁门
It's already closed. Chris gave me the keys to lock up.
出了什么事
What is wrong?
我想我的婚姻
My marriage, I think my marriage is...
应该是完蛋了
...is kind of over.
不会吧  为什么
Oh, no! Why?
因为卡罗尔是个女同性恋
Because Carol's a lesbian.
而我不是
And I'm not one.
而且这显然不是一时兴起混搭一下
And apparently it's not a mix-and-match situation.
天哪
Oh, my God!
我真不敢相信
I don't believe it!
可怜的孩子
Oh, you poor bunny.
我是白痴
I'm an idiot.
我早该看出来了
I should have seen it.
卡罗尔和我出门时
I mean, Carol and I would be out,
她总喜欢盯着漂亮姑娘看
and she'd see some beautiful woman...
她会说  "罗斯  你看她"
...and she'd be "Ross! Look at her!"
我还觉得
And I'd think...
天哪  我老婆真酷
"God, my wife is cool."
你觉得那个苏珊是她的情人吗
Hey, do you think that Susan person is her lover?
我现在知道了
Well, now I do!
对不起
I'm sorry.
都七年了
Seven years!
我们在一起七年了
I mean, we've been together seven years.
她是唯一爱过我的女人
She's the only woman who's ever loved me.
也是我唯一有过...
She's the only woman I've ever....
罗斯
Ross.
真好
This is nice.
我知道  很棒对不对
I know. It is, isn't it?
我是说真的  摸起来好舒服
No, I mean it. This feels really good.
是纯棉的吗
Is it 100% cotton?
对  而且还是特价品
Yeah! And I got it on sale too.
我该走了
Anyway, I should go.
有一个救生员正要拆除核弹
One of the lifeguards was just about to dismantle a nuclear device.
我们待会可以去喝一杯
If you want to get a drink later, we can.
听起来不错
Yeah, that sounds great.
还有  事情会...
Oh, and listen, it's gonna be...
我知道
I know.
谢了
Thanks.
搞不好可以避免
Maybe this wouldn't have happened
要是我再温柔体贴一些  或是
if I'd been more nurturing or...
多注意她一点  或是我
I'd paid more attention or I...
有子宫
had a uterus.
-我真不敢相信  -我知道
- I can't believe it. - I know.
你不该受这种折磨  真的  罗斯
No, you know, you don't deserve this. You don't, Ross.
-你人这么好  -谢谢
- You're really... You're so good. - Thanks.
而且你很体贴
And you're so sweet.
-谢谢  -心肠又好
- Thanks. - And you're kind.
谢谢
Thanks.
过来
Come here.
等一下
Wait, wait, wait.
别管了
It's okay.
等一下  我的脚卡在球洞里了
Wait, wait, wait! My foot is stuck in the pocket.
什么
What?
我弄不出来
I can't get it out.
女生可不想听到这种话
That's not something a girl wants to hear.
你别逗我
Come on, don't start.
怎么了
What?
这些烂球好碍事
Stupid balls are in the way.
好吧
Oh, well.
这不是最有建设性的解决方式
That probably wouldn't have been the most constructive solution.
你的脸上有粉笔灰
You have chalk on your face.
罗斯  你说得对
Ross, you're right.
我怎么会以为这是真的草皮呢
I don't know why I always thought this was real grass.
亲爱的  你还好吗
Honey, you okay?
我老婆是同性恋
My wife's a lesbian.
酷
Cool!
罗斯  乔伊  乔伊  罗斯
Ross, Joey. Joey, Ross.
不敢相信你竟然回来了
I can't believe you came back.
什么都不要说
Don't say anything.
我不想说话  我不想思考
I don't wanna speak. I don't wanna think.
我只要你抱紧我  亲吻我  跟我做爱
I just want you to take me and kiss me and make love to me
就在此时此地
right here right now.
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rachel, Rachel.
-干嘛  -你错过出口了
- What? - You missed the exit.
对不起
Sorry.
真是的  你在想什么
My God, what were you thinking about?
巴瑞
Barry.